<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Marcus Tang Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://marcustxk.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Marcus Tang Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marcustxk.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Deployment Triggers</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/contributions/deploy-triggers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/contributions/deploy-triggers/</guid>
      <description>Addressed pretty significant page load performance issue founde in larger deployments. Eliminates uses of intensive backend query, replacing it with an asynchronous API call against a lucene index. This change reduces page load from from 2+ minutes to nearly instant, with an incredibly responsive UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swappee</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/creations/swappee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 22:54:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/creations/swappee/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Added Docker Build Status Badge to shields.io</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/contributions/shields-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 17:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/contributions/shields-docker/</guid>
      <description>Shields.io is a massive library of badges that can be inserted into project README&amp;rsquo;s or websites displaying various statuses (code coverage, health, version, etc). Support for docker was missing the current build health, and was a pretty trivial addition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schema.org Structured Data documentation fixes</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/contributions/schema-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 17:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/contributions/schema-org/</guid>
      <description>While adding Structured Data to a client&amp;rsquo;s website I found some example JSON that was invalid. Simple contribution to cleanup the user documentation providing syntactically valid JSON documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4th Place, Ninja Van Code Dojo Hackathon 2022</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/awards/ninja-van-code-dojo-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/awards/ninja-van-code-dojo-2022/</guid>
      <description>Description Code Dojo was a 36 hour Hackathon where my team of 4 worked to innovate and prototype ideas that can improve logistics and Ninja Van&amp;rsquo;s operations and service quality. Ninja Van is a leading courier company in Singapore and across Southeast Asia, with more than 67,000 staff and delivery personnel and handles around 2 million parcels a day across Southeast Asia.
Solution Ninja Scheduler is the bot designed for busy people who are unavailable to receive their package on the actual delivery day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Top 8 Teams” Award Winner, Hack&amp;Roll 2022</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/awards/hack-n-roll-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/awards/hack-n-roll-2022/</guid>
      <description>Description Hack&amp;amp;Roll is Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest student-run hackathon, with 532 participants in Hack&amp;amp;Roll 2022. I was inspired to improve NUSMods, a student-run open source project allowing students to plan timetables and modules, as its current module review system was under utilised by students as it was cumbersome and slow to write long reviews.
Solution Leading a team of 4 and in 24 hours, we came up with Ratings, an alternative review system inspired by Glassdoor that aims to encourage more students to provide feedback by streamlining the process as well as allowing prospective students of a module to better understand the module easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1st Place, 18th SoC Term Project Showcase (STePS)</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/awards/18th-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/awards/18th-steps/</guid>
      <description>Description Source Academy is an open-source immersive online experiential environment for learning programming, developed in the School of Computing at the National University of Singapore, currently headed by the Source Academy 2021 leadership team.
Every year, freshmen in the School of Computing will take CS1101S, a module that introduces the concepts of programming and computational problem solving, and is the first and foremost introductory module to computing. This module’s course material is mainly conveyed through the Source Academy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Top 8 Teams” Award Winner, Hack&amp;Roll 2021</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/awards/hack-n-roll-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/awards/hack-n-roll-2021/</guid>
      <description>Description Hack&amp;amp;Roll is Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest student-run hackathon, with 473 participants in Hack&amp;amp;Roll 2021. We often come across instances where we have to arrange, with friends, a timing to meetup, be it for a group project or a leisure activity. It is often troublesome to come into an agreement of a common free time slot. Therefore, it is convenient to have Meetups, a planner modification for NUSMods, a student-run open source project allowing students to plan timetables and modules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOSH release for Bamboo &amp; Remote Agents</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</guid>
      <description>BOSH (Bosh Outer SHell) &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; is an open source tool for release engineering, deployment, lifecycle management, and monitoring of distributed systems.&amp;rdquo; And it&amp;rsquo;s amazingly powerful. This examples uses BOSH to provision an Alassian vendor app running on JDK along with the support Postgres database and agents to support it. The releases manages the health of services and will automatically provision, start/stop processes across the various services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forcing Visits to use SSL</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/blog/force-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/blog/force-ssl/</guid>
      <description>Intro Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter whether it&amp;rsquo;s a CakePHP app for a client, your own personal CMS, or any other web based application. If your passing around passwords or other sensitive info you should really implement SSL. SSL provides 2 main perks to your visitors.
First it encrypts all communication that flies across the web. This prevents curious or devious billies from getting your secrets. Secondly it ensures to the user that your server is in fact who it claims, and not a nasty &amp;lsquo;man in the middle&amp;quot; attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Marketplace Plugins</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/creations/marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/creations/marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Multiple plugins used by thousands of teams that provide enhanced functionality of Atlassian’s core products (primarily JIRA and Bamboo) to enrich CI/CD capabilities, DevOps automation, or productivity. Functionality spans user interface, web services and persistence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker image for Bitbucket CI/CD Pipelines  &#34;shipit&#34;</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/creations/docker-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/creations/docker-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Provides required dependencies and additional utilities to simplify and codify the process of building, testing and delivering Atlassian plugins all the way to the live marketplace. Executes integration/AUT level tests against all stated compatible versions for the productUploads generated artifact to Atlassian marketplaceProvides corresponding metadata indicating version, release notes, and compatibility</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs] home = [&amp;#34;HTML&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;JSON&amp;#34;] Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
