<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Heroku on Marcus Tang Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://marcustxk.com/tags/heroku/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Heroku on Marcus Tang Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marcustxk.com/tags/heroku/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Developer Student Club - Project Siew Dai</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/project-siew-dai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/project-siew-dai/</guid>
      <description>Description Diabetes Singapore (DS) is a non-profit organisation focused on raising awareness and providing education, counselling and support to people with diabetes, their families and the community in order to empower them to lead a healthy and productive life. Today, DS runs two clinics and two mobile bus clinics that serve to provide care and education dedicated to Diabetes in Singapore.
Problem Statement DS currently lacks a database and a corresponding database management system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4th Place, Ninja Van Code Dojo Hackathon 2022</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/awards/ninja-van-code-dojo-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/awards/ninja-van-code-dojo-2022/</guid>
      <description>Description Code Dojo was a 36 hour Hackathon where my team of 4 worked to innovate and prototype ideas that can improve logistics and Ninja Van&amp;rsquo;s operations and service quality. Ninja Van is a leading courier company in Singapore and across Southeast Asia, with more than 67,000 staff and delivery personnel and handles around 2 million parcels a day across Southeast Asia.
Solution Ninja Scheduler is the bot designed for busy people who are unavailable to receive their package on the actual delivery day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
