<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Java on Marcus Tang Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://marcustxk.com/tags/java/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Java on Marcus Tang Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marcustxk.com/tags/java/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Swappee</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/swappee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/swappee/</guid>
      <description>Description A platform allowing users in a community to list items online to trade, facilitating the trading process using Spring, React and Elasticsearch Users can search/filter for items by name, user, or items the user has previously liked Emails will be sent to the user if an item matching their preference was uploaded Users can make trade requests, accept, and review other users upon trading Item cards in each user’s inventory will be swapped upon trading and each item will have a history log on its previous trades and owners </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gitGud</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/git-gud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/git-gud/</guid>
      <description>Description gitGud is a desktop application for storing and managing your friends&amp;rsquo; gaming information and schedules. It is dedicated to gamers like you and provides a gamer-themed experience with a focus on increasing your efficiency through its typing-based interface.
Previously, keeping track of all of yours friends&amp;rsquo; gaming information and schedules can be difficult and time-consuming. However, with gitGud, there is no need to get tilted (frustrated) by this anymore as gitGud provides you with a convenient platform to manage essential gaming information of your fellow gamer friends.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
