<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>React on Marcus Tang Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://marcustxk.com/tags/react/</link>
    <description>Recent content in React on Marcus Tang Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marcustxk.com/tags/react/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Developer Student Club - Project Sight Words [Ongoing]</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/project-sight-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/project-sight-words/</guid>
      <description>Description In collaboration with Dyslexic Association of Singapore (DAS), Project Sight Words aims to make learning fun for dyslexic students with an online learning platform that is engaging and customized to their learning needs by using a multi-sensory approach. The platform will have two fronts, a progressive web app to teach students how to read and write through interactive learning, as well as a teacher management portal to help educators manage their lessons and students progress more conveniently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Developer Student Club - Project Siew Dai</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/project-siew-dai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/project-siew-dai/</guid>
      <description>Description Diabetes Singapore (DS) is a non-profit organisation focused on raising awareness and providing education, counselling and support to people with diabetes, their families and the community in order to empower them to lead a healthy and productive life. Today, DS runs two clinics and two mobile bus clinics that serve to provide care and education dedicated to Diabetes in Singapore.
Problem Statement DS currently lacks a database and a corresponding database management system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Top 8 Teams” Award Winner, Hack&amp;Roll 2022</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/awards/hack-n-roll-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/awards/hack-n-roll-2022/</guid>
      <description>Description Hack&amp;amp;Roll is Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest student-run hackathon, with 532 participants in Hack&amp;amp;Roll 2022. I was inspired to improve NUSMods, a student-run open source project allowing students to plan timetables and modules, as its current module review system was under utilised by students as it was cumbersome and slow to write long reviews.
Solution Leading a team of 4 and in 24 hours, we came up with Ratings, an alternative review system inspired by Glassdoor that aims to encourage more students to provide feedback by streamlining the process as well as allowing prospective students of a module to better understand the module easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1st Place, 18th SoC Term Project Showcase (STePS)</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/awards/18th-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/awards/18th-steps/</guid>
      <description>Description Source Academy is an open-source immersive online experiential environment for learning programming, developed in the School of Computing at the National University of Singapore, currently headed by the Source Academy 2021 leadership team.
Every year, freshmen in the School of Computing will take CS1101S, a module that introduces the concepts of programming and computational problem solving, and is the first and foremost introductory module to computing. This module’s course material is mainly conveyed through the Source Academy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Source Academy Module System</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/source-academy-module-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/source-academy-module-system/</guid>
      <description>Description Source Academy is an open-source immersive online experiential environment for learning programming, developed in the School of Computing at the National University of Singapore, currently headed by the Source Academy 2021 leadership team.
Every year, freshmen in the School of Computing will take CS1101S, a module that introduces the concepts of programming and computational problem solving, and is the first and foremost introductory module to computing. This module’s course material is mainly conveyed through the Source Academy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Top 8 Teams” Award Winner, Hack&amp;Roll 2021</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/awards/hack-n-roll-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/awards/hack-n-roll-2021/</guid>
      <description>Description Hack&amp;amp;Roll is Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest student-run hackathon, with 473 participants in Hack&amp;amp;Roll 2021. We often come across instances where we have to arrange, with friends, a timing to meetup, be it for a group project or a leisure activity. It is often troublesome to come into an agreement of a common free time slot. Therefore, it is convenient to have Meetups, a planner modification for NUSMods, a student-run open source project allowing students to plan timetables and modules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>React With Redux Projects</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/react-with-redux-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/react-with-redux-projects/</guid>
      <description>React With Redux Projects Various react projects developed during my journey of learning React and Redux: Streams A simple streaming website that allows a user to stream as well as users to watch streams created by other users. When signed in (via Google OAuth 2.0), a user can create a stream. Only the owner of a stream can edit or delete their own stream. Users can stream their screen via Open Broadcaster Software (OBS) to the created stream.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
