<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Marcus Tang Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://marcustxk.com/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Marcus Tang Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marcustxk.com/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>4th Place, Ninja Van Code Dojo Hackathon 2022</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/awards/ninja-van-code-dojo-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/awards/ninja-van-code-dojo-2022/</guid>
      <description>Description Code Dojo was a 36 hour Hackathon where my team of 4 worked to innovate and prototype ideas that can improve logistics and Ninja Van&amp;rsquo;s operations and service quality. Ninja Van is a leading courier company in Singapore and across Southeast Asia, with more than 67,000 staff and delivery personnel and handles around 2 million parcels a day across Southeast Asia.
Solution Ninja Scheduler is the bot designed for busy people who are unavailable to receive their package on the actual delivery day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOSH release for Bamboo &amp; Remote Agents</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</guid>
      <description>BOSH (Bosh Outer SHell) &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; is an open source tool for release engineering, deployment, lifecycle management, and monitoring of distributed systems.&amp;rdquo; And it&amp;rsquo;s amazingly powerful. This examples uses BOSH to provision an Alassian vendor app running on JDK along with the support Postgres database and agents to support it. The releases manages the health of services and will automatically provision, start/stop processes across the various services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker image for Bitbucket CI/CD Pipelines  &#34;shipit&#34;</title>
      <link>https://marcustxk.com/projects/creations/docker-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marcustxk.com/projects/creations/docker-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Provides required dependencies and additional utilities to simplify and codify the process of building, testing and delivering Atlassian plugins all the way to the live marketplace. Executes integration/AUT level tests against all stated compatible versions for the productUploads generated artifact to Atlassian marketplaceProvides corresponding metadata indicating version, release notes, and compatibility</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
